title: Start
tags: 
colorID: 0
position: 592,181
---
I know, memories can be hard things to swallow.
<<showInventories GameManager>>
-> —Where am I. 
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_I>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>
Let's start this thing again.
-> —Get out of my head.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_GetOut>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>
Do you remember how to do this? Press '1' and '2' to respond to my questions
-> —...What the hell?
-> —Press what?
Drag your cursor to relocate and refocus your memories. Try to keep the good ones close to you, and push the bad ones out. 
-> —You're not making sense.
Don’t let them clutter up your conscience, or we’ll have to start over.  
-> —... 
Just tell us what happened. We can see your memories, after all. 
-> —My memories of what?
Anyway, let's try again. It's a new day. Tell me your name.
-> —S.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_S>>
-> —B. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_B>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>
You didn’t say that last time. Tell me again, what’s your name?
-> —S. 
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_S>>
-> —B. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_B>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>
Let's just move on. Tell me about the first time you met Riley.
-> —Who? 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_Who>>
-> —Okay. What do you want to know? 
<<waitTillEmpty>>

When did you meet them?
-> —There were a couple of times.
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_CoupleOfTimes>>

-> —I only met Riley once.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Once>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Did you speak to them? 
-> —Yes.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Yes>>

-> —No. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_No>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Try to remember for me. Did you?
-> —Yes.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Yes>>

-> —No. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_No>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Good. So, do you know where B. is now?
-> —Yes.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Yes>>

-> —He's with you. 
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_WithYou>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

What did Riley do to B.?
-> —I never found out. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_NeverFoundOut>>

-> —Took him away.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_TookHim>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Has B. been having trouble breathing?
-> —Yes. I told you this. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_IToldYou>>

-> —No. That's wrong.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_No>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Okay. Then, can I set the scene for you? It might help?
-> —...

When B. was found he was stuggling to breathe. He said Riley said it was payback for what you did. 
-> —Payback...
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Payback>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

First, the rash. Then, the sleep. Not being able to sleep. And third...
-> —He has trouble breathing. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_Breathing>> 

-> —There was something wrong with his eyes.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Eyes>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

That's right. You remember now. I can see it in that head of yours.
-> —I do.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_IDo>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Last time we had this session with you, you showed us a fragment of your memory where you saw Riley and B. They were in an argument. Did this happen before or after you met Riley?
-> —Before. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_Before>>

-> —After
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_After>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

And had you met Riley before?
-> —Just a few times. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_AFewTimes>>

-> —I've only met Riley once.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Once>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Is Riley in this room right now?
-> Yes. 
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Yes>>

-> No. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_No>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Would Riley come out and join us for a chat?
-> Okay.
-> No.

Okay. That's alright. Tell Riley I said hi. 
-> I will.

Listen, Shawna. I can ask again, or I can easily push a bit deeper into your head. I can see you trying to hide those memories now. Was it you, or was it Riley then?
-> —... 
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Yes>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

I'm sorry. Sorry to dwell on it. It's horrible. Did you do this to B., or did Riley do this?
-> —I did it. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_IDidIt>>

-> —Riley.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_Riley>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

What did Riley do to B.?
-> —Riley killed him. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_KilledHim>> 

-> —Riley took him away.
	<<addItem GameManager Truth_TookHimAway>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

And so when we found B. sitting on the side of the road – I mean, he wouldn’t even talk to us, he wouldn’t even tell us where he’d been.
-> —You think I left him there?
-> It wasn't me. I told you this.
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_ItWasntMe>>

He couldn’t walk. He tried to stand up but his legs just sort of caved in.
-> —I didn’t mean for that to happen to him. 
	<<addItem GameManager Lie_DidntMeanForThat>>

-> —It was punishment. 
	<<addItem Dispenser Inventory Lie_Punishment>>
<<waitTillEmpty>>

And he was blind. He thought I was Riley.
-> He deserved it.
-> He asked for it.

So you admit it then?
-> Yes.
	<<addItem Dispenser Inventory Truth_Yes>>
-> No.
	<<addItem Dispenser Inventory Lie_No>>	
<<waitTillEmpty>>

Are you trying to hide your memory of it?
-> …

You realise I can see what you’re thinking.
-> … 

You’re going to stay quiet now?
-> …

I’ll give you another chance before we take B. back into our custody. He’s not safe with you. 
-> …

Okay, then. I'll pull this thing out now and leave you to your own thoughts. We'll try this again tomorrow. 
-> Wait...

Have a good day. :) 